Guide to the King County Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- King County Labor Council records, 1970-2003; 1990-2000; 1940-002; 20.00 cubic ft. 20 boxes
  - SERIES II: SUBJECT SERIES
    - Out Front Labor Coalition, 1997 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers, 1994- 1998 (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Sandra Oleson, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12/22)
    - Olympic Pipe Line Company, 1999 (Box-folder 12/23)
    - One-by-One USA, 1995 (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Olympics Bid, 2012, 1998 (Box-folder 12/25)
    - OPEIU Local 8 Benefits, 1999- 2000 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Organizer - Resumes, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 12/27)
    - Pacific Coast Tradeswomen Summit (1997), 1996 (Box-folder 12/28)
    - Paycheck Protection Act, 1996 (Box-folder 12/29)
    - People for Puget Sound, 1993 (Box-folder 12/30)
    - Phone Banking (KCLC Delegates), Undated (Box-folder 12/31)
    - Phone Banking, 1990 (Box-folder 12/32)
    - Pico (South Korea) Workers Union, 1991 (Box-folder 12/33)
    - National Report on Population and Development, 1993 (Box-folder 12/34)
    - Port Coalition Misc. (1 of 2), 1992- 2001 (Box-folder 12/35)
    - Port Coalition Misc. (2 of 2), 1991 (Box-folder 12/36)
    - Port Commissioners/Districts, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Port JOBS (1 of 12), 1996- 2001 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Port JOBS (2 of 12), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Port JOBS (3 of 12), 1994- 1995 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Port JOBS (4 of 12), 1999 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Port JOBS (5 of 12), 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Port JOBS (6 of 12), 1996-1998 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Port JOBS (7 of 12), 1994- 1996 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Port JOBS (8 of 12), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Port JOBS (9 of 12), 1993 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Port JOBS (10 of 12), 1993 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Port JOBS (11 of 12), 1991- 1993 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Port JOBS (12 of 12), 1991 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Port JOBS Executive Director Search 1997 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Port of Seattle, 1994- 1995 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Portworks (Business and Labor), 1992- 1996 (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Port of Seattle (1 of 2), 1986-1994 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Port of Seattle (2 of 2), 1991 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Port of SEattle APL Expansion Program, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Port of Seattle, Bell Harbor International Conference Center, 1995 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Port of SEattle, Chuck Lare, 1996- 1998 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Port of SEattle, Columbia Research Group, 1995 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Port of Seattle, Global Labor Management, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Port of Seattle, Harbor Maintenence Tax, 1999 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Port of Seattle, Independent Trucking, 1996 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Port of Seattle, Joint Labor Management Retreat, 1993 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Port of SEattle Reorganization Plan, 1995 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Port of Seattle, Southwest Harbor Project, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Port of Seattle, Westin, Marriott, 1997 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Poverty & Race Research Action Council, 1994 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Press Release Media List, Undated (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Prevailing Wage, 1991- 2001 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Prevailing Wage - Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Prevailing Wage - Association of Washington Cities, 1995 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Private Industry Council - Seattle/King County, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Progressive America, 1999 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Progressive Electoral Coalition, Undated (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Project Labor Agreements, 1994- 2000 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Puget Sound Cooperative Federation, 1994 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Puget Sound Regional Council (1 of 3), 1994, 2000 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Puget Sound Regional Council (2 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Puget Sound Regional Council (3 of 3), 1993 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Puget Sound Transportation Investment Program, 1993 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Puyallup Fair, 1989- 1995 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Pyramid Communications, Undated (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Rainbow Coalition, 1993 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Rallies, 1969- 1996 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Rebound, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Regional Transit (See Sound Transit), 1993-2000 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Renton, City of, 1998 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Retreat 1997 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Executive Board Retreat 1994 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Retreat 1991 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Retreat 1992 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Right to Organize, 1998 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Roosevelt Square Redevelopment, 1997 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Rutgers University, 1993 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - State Route 509, 1996 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Saturn, 1996- 1998 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - SOIL - Save Our Industrial Land, 1996- 1998 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - School to Work Coordinating Board - Seattle Public Schools, 1997 (Box-folder 15/19)
    - School to Work, 1995- 1996 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - School to Work Opportunities, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Seattle Airport Third Runway, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 15/22)
    - Seattle Chamber of Commerce, 1988- 2001 (Box-folder 15/23)
    - Seattle 18 (NLRB Rally Arrests), 1993 (Box-folder 15/24)
    - Seattle, City of, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 15/25)
    - Seattle City Apprenticeship Opportunities Program, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 15/26)
    - Seattle (City of) AATF (Apprenticeship Advisory Task Force) (1 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 15/27)
    - Seattle (City of) AATF (Apprenticeship Advisory Task Force) (2 of 2), 1995-1997 (Box-folder 15/28)
    - Seattle, City of -- Business and Labor Committee, 1994 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Seattle, City of -- Commercial Advisory Panel, 1994 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Seattle, City of -- Construction Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Seattle, City of -- Downtown Action Plan, 1993 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Seattle, City of -- Economic Development Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Seattle, City of -- Noise Ordinance, 1999 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Seattle, City of -- Mayor Paul Schell, 1997- 1998 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Seattle Comprehensive Plan, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Seattle Center, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Seattle City Council, 1990- 1999 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Seattle Commons (1 of 3), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Seattle Commons (2 of 3), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Seattle Commons AFL-CIO Project, 1994 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Seattle Commons (3 of 3), 1993 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Seattle Community Colleges/KCLC Workforce Training, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Seattle Community Colleges/KCLC Leadership Comm, 1998 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Seattle Housing Authority (for negotiations with OPEIU Loc. 8, see affil. file for OPEIU Loc. 8), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - Seattle Jobs Initiative (MOU Negotiations - Annie Casey), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - Seattle Labor Temple Association (1 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - Seattle Labor Temple Association (2 of 3), 1995-1997 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - Seattle Labor Temple Association (3 of 3), 1992-1995 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Seattle/King County Health Department, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - Seattle Plan - Organizing, 1993 (Box-folder 16/23)
    - Seattle Police Management Association, 1997 (Box-folder 16/24)
    - Seattle Progressive Coalition, 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Seattle School District (1 of 2), 1993- 1997 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Seattle School District (2 of 2), 1989- 1993 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Seattle Seahawks, 1987-2001 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Seattle Transportation Group, 1994 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Seattle Water Department, 1994 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Seattle Vocational Institute, 1991- 1995 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Puget Sound Shipyards Industrial Jobs Commission, 1989 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Shoreline Community College, 1998 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Snohomish County Labor Council, 1996- 1999 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Solicitations for Contributions, 1993- 1998 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Song, Oswald & Mondress, 1998 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Sound Transit, 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Speeches, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Spirit of Puget Sound, 1990- 1993 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Staley Catterpillar - Illinois, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - State Farm Insurance, 1993 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - United Steelworkers of America, 1995- 1996 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Team PIC (Private Industry Council), 1982- 1997 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Tenants Union, 1995 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Third House, 1995- 1999 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Tribes of Washington State, 1996 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers (UAW), Region 9, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 17/22)
    - U.S. Army School of the Americas, 1998 (Box-folder 17/23)
    - U.S. Congress Progressive Caucus, 1994 (Box-folder 17/24)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1993- 1995 (Box-folder 17/25)
    - U.S. Secretary of Labor / Alexis Herman, 1999 (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Unemployment Law Project 1993-1999 (Box-folder 17/27)
    - Uniformed Command Association, 1995 (Box-folder 17/28)
    - United Way, 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 17/29)
    - University of Washington - 1994, Governor's Committee, 1993- 1994 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - University of Washington - Harry Bridges Center, 1994- 1998 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Washington Coalition for Occupational Safety and Health (WashCOSH), 1993- 1998 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Washington Alliance for Manufacturing, 1995 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Washington Citizen Action, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Washington Community Housing Network, 1997 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Washington Council for Fair Elections, 1997 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Washington Education Association, 1989- 1995 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - WEAVE - Washington Environmental Alliance for Voter Education, 1994- 1997 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Washington Environmental Council, 1994- 1996 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Washington Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Washington News Council, 1998 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Washington Single Payer Action Netwark (WASPAN), 1998 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Washington State Public Interest Research Group (WashPIRG), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Washington Toxics Coalition, 1995, 1998 (Box-folder 18/15)
    - We Do the Work, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 18/16)
    - Welfare Reform, 1996- 2000 (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Welfare Rights Coaltion, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Wells Fargo (Steelworkers Dispute), 1998 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Western Labor Press Association (Scanner), 1987-1998 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Western States Center, 1993- 1995 (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Women in Trades, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Woodland Park Zoo, 1996- 1999 (Box-folder 18/23)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1999 (Box-folder 18/24)
    - Memorial Day - 1998 (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1997 (Box-folder 18/26)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - Misc., 1987-1995 (Box-folder 18/27)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1996 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 18/28)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1996 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 18/29)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1995 (Box-folder 18/30)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1994 (Box-folder 18/31)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1992 (Box-folder 18/32)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1991 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Workers' Memorial Day - 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Workers' Monument, 1995, 2002 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Workers' Rights Boards, 1999 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Workforce Alliance, 1996- 1997 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Workforce Development, 1999 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Workforce Investment Act - 1999 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Workforce Training & Education Board, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - World Affairs Council, 1993- 1997 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - World Trade Organization Protests (1 of 2), November 1999-December 1999 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - World Trade Organization Protests (2 of 2), February 1999-October 1999 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Ron's World Trade Organization Protests File (1 of 2), May 1999-December 1999 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Ron's World Trade Organization Protests File (2 of 2), March 1999-May 1999 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - WTO Expenses, 1999 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - World War II Memorial, 1998 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Henry Wu, 1995- 1996 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Washington STate Arts Commission, 1994 (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Washington State Attorney General's Office, 1984, 1994 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Washington State Bar Association, 1996 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Washington STate Department of Community, Trade, & Economic Development, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 19/)
    - Washington State Department of Fish & Wildlife, 1996, 2000 (Box-folder 19/)
    - Washington State Insurance Commission, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Washington State Board of Industrial Insurance Appeals, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Washington State Employment Security, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Washington Health Care Campaign, 1993 (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Washington State Liquor Control Board, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Washington State Prevailing Wage, 1988, 1995 (Box-folder 19/27)
    - Washington State Public Employment Relations Commission, 1996 (Box-folder 19/28)
    - Washington State Senate Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 19/29)
    - WSLC Activists List, 1995 (Box-folder 19/30)
    - WSLC High School Students Summer School, 1997 (Box-folder 19/31)
  - SERIES III: COMMITTEE ON POLITICAL EDUCATION (COPE), 1992-1999 (Box-folder 20/1-20/44)
    - COPE 1999 Mailings (Box-folder 20/1)
    - COPE 1999 Misc. (Box-folder 20/2)
    - COPE 1999 Candidates (Box-folder 20/3)
    - COPE 1998 Judicial Races (Box-folder 20/4)
    - COPE 1998 State Legislative Races (Box-folder 20/5)
    - COPE 1998 Minimum Wage Initiative I- 688 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - COPE 1998 Federal Races (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Initiative 200 (NO! on 200) COPE 1998 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - COPE 1998 GOTV & Labor 98 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - City of Seattle Proposition 1 (yes)/Initiative 45 (no), 1998 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - COPE 1998 HR 950 (includes 1997 HR 1951) Jobs Bill, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - COPE 1998 WSLC (Box-folder 20/12)
    - COPE 1997 City (Box-folder 20/13)
    - COPE 1997 County (Box-folder 20/14)
    - COPE 1997 Initiative 677 (Box-folder 20/15)
    - COPE 1997 State (Box-folder 20/16)
    - COPE 1997 KCLC/WSLC/AFL-CIO (Box-folder 20/17)
    - COPE 1997 WSLC (Box-folder 20/18)
    - COPE 1996, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 20/19)
    - COPE 1996 Legislators (Box-folder 20/20)
    - COPE 1996 (Box-folder 20/21)
    - COPE 1996 Seattle City Council, Pos. 6 (Box-folder 20/22)
    - COPE 1996 State Offices (Box-folder 20/23)
    - COPE 1996 1st Congressional District (Rick White) (Box-folder 20/24)
    - COPE 1996 9th Congressional District (Randy Tate) (Box-folder 20/25)
    - School Levy 1996 (Box-folder 20/26)
    - COPE 1995 Other (Box-folder 20/27)
    - COPE 1995 County, City (Box-folder 20/28)
    - COPE 1995 (Misc.) (Box-folder 20/29)
    - 1995 Legislative Action Committee Meetings (Box-folder 20/30)
    - Initiative 640 (Salmon, Steelhead, etc.), 1995 (Box-folder 20/31)
    - HR 210 Postal Service Privatization, 1995 (Box-folder 20/32)
    - Omnibus Counterterrorism Act of 1995 (Box-folder 20/33)
    - COPE 1995 Legislative Session and National Legislation (Box-folder 20/34)
    - 1994 Election (Misc.) (Box-folder 20/35)
    - COPE 1994 (Box-folder 20/36)
    - 1994 Candidates State and Local not endorsed (Box-folder 20/37)
    - COPE 1994 Endorsed Candidates (Box-folder 20/38)
    - Legislative Action Committee, 1994 (Box-folder 20/39)
    - Voter Registration, 1992 (Box-folder 20/40)
    - Chris Gregoire Attorney General COPE 1992 (Box-folder 20/41)
    - Mike Heavey 34th Dist. Rep., Pos. 1 1992 COPE (Box-folder 20/42)
    - Michael Lowry Governor 1992 WSLC (Box-folder 20/43)
    - Legislation - Federal 1992 COPE (Box-folder 20/44)
- King County Labor Council records, 1999-2008; 1940-003; 3 cubic feet 3 boxes
  Donated by Central Labor Council of Seattle.
  Correspondence, minutes, financial records, reports, photographs, ephemera, membership records, committee records; 1889-1970 (bulk 1950-1969). The bulk consists of files of Chet W. Ramage, who was Executive Secretary of the Council until 1968. The bulk consists of files of Chet W. Ramage, who was Executive Secretary of the Council from Oct. 1959 through 1968.
  - Series I: Correspondence, Minutes, Fliers, 1999-2008
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 1999-February 1999 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 1999-April 1999 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 1999-June 1999 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 1999-August 1999 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, September 1999-October 1999 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, November 1999-December 1999 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2000-February 2000 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 2000-April 2000 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2000-June 2000 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2000-July 2000 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, August 2000-August 2000 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, September 2000-October 2000 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, November 2000-December 2000 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2001-February 2001 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 2001-March 2001 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, April 2001-April 2001 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2001-May 2001 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, June 2001-June 2001 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2001-August 2001 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, September 2001-October 2001 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, November 2001-December 2001 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2002-March 2002 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, April 2002-April 2002 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2002-May 2002 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, June 2002-June 2002 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2002-September 2002 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, October 2002-October 2002 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, November 2002-September 2002 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2002-February 2002 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 2003-April 2003 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2003-June 2003 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2002-August 2002 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, September 2003-October 2003 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, November 2003-December 2003 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2004-January 2004 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, February 2004-February 2004 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 2004-March 2004 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, April 2004-April 2004 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2004-May 2004 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, June 2004-July 2004 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, August 2004-September 2004 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, October 2004-December 2004 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2005-March 2005 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, April 2005-May 2005 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, June 2005-June 2005 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2005-August 2005 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, September 2005-October 2005 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, November 2005-December 2005 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2006-February 2006 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 2006-April 2006 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2006-June 2006 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2006-September 2006 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, October 2006-December 2006 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2007-March 2007 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, April 2007-June 2007 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2007-July 2007 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, August 2007-September 2007 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, October 2007-December 2007 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, January 2008-February 2008 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, March 2008-April 2008 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, May 2008-June 2008 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, July 2008-September 2008 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Flyers, October 2008-December 2008 (Box-folder 3/21)
- King County Labor Council. Provisional Trades Section minutes, 1935-1971; 1940-004; 0.42 cubic ft. 1 box
  Section of the Central Labor Council of Seattle formed by representatives from various local unions, including: Bakers, Bakery Salesmen, Bartenders, Butcher Workers, Candy Workers, Cooks, Coopers, Cracker Bakers, Delivery Salesmen, Flour and Cereal, Hotel and Club Service Employees, Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Ice Men, Macaroni Workers, Meat Cutters, Milk Men, Produce Workers, Retail Food and Drug Clerks, Waiters, and Waitresses.
  Minutes of the Provisional Trades Section
  Open to all users
  Donated by Ross Rieder, 11/1/2004.
- Martin Luther King, Jr. County Labor Council records, 1965-2012; 1940-005; 6.56 cubic feet 7 boxes
  Committee on Political Education (COPE) Records (2000-2005), Meeting Minutes (1998-2012), General Correspondence (1993-2009), Delegate Roll Call Sign-In Ledgers (1965-1977)
  No restrictions on access.
  King County Labor Council--Nicole Grant and Robin Duda
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE) Records, 2000-2005; Series 1 (Box-folder 1/1-3/20)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, County, 2002 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Judicial, 2002 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Federal, 2002 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislative, 2002 (Box-folder 1/4.1)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislative, 2002 (Box-folder 1/4.2)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, State Legislative, 2002 (Box-folder 1/4.3)
    - Initiatives, Bonds & Levies, 2002 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Seattle City Council, 2003 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Other Cities, 2003 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Port of Seattle, 2003 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, Judicial Races, 2003 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Initiatives & Referendums, 2003 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Seattle School District Races, 2003 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Initiatives and Referendums, 2003 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Public Disclosure Commmission Reports (PDC "Reports"), 2003 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Committee on Political Education 2000 - Political Action Committee (Box-folder 1/16)